Thomas Tingey Craven Papers
Thomas Tingey Craven Papers
- Miscellanea
  - Other documents (Box 2)
Perry, Matthew C. 1843 Jan 23, Navy Yard, Brooklyn, N. Y., to A. Lewis 1843 Aug 1, USS Saratoga, Mesurado Roads, West Coast of Africa, to H. S. Stellwagen 1843 Aug 16, USS Saratoga, Mesurado Roads, West Coast of Africa, to H. S. Stellwagen 1843 Sep 11, USS Saratoga, Porto Grande, West Africa 1843 Oct 12, US Frigate Macedonian, Port Praya, West Coast of Africa 1843 Oct 12, US Frigate Macedonian, Port Praya, West Coast of Africa 1843 Oct 13, US Frigate Macedonian, Port Praya, West Coast of Africa 1843 Dec 27, US Frigate Macedonian, at sea West Coast of Africa 1844 Jan 2, USS Macedonian off Cape Mesurado, West Coast of Africa 1844 Jan 2, USS Macedonian off Cape Mesurado, West Coast of Africa 1844 Jan 4, USS Macedonian off Monrovia, West Africa 1844 Mar 6, Port Praya, West Coast of Africa, to F. Gardner (?) (copy) 1844 Mar 6, Port Praya, West Coast of Africa (2 letters) 1844 Mar 6, US Frigate Macedonian, Port Praya, to To the commander of any US Store Vessel that may arrive at Port Praya with provisions and store for the African Squadron (copy) 1844 Apr 10, Funchal Island off Madeira 1844 May 22, USS Macedonian, Port Praya, West Africa 1844 May 22, USS Macedonian, Port Praya, West Africa 1844 May 22, USS Macedonian, Port Praya, West Africa 1844 May 24, USS Macedonian, Port Praya, West Africa 1844 May 24, USS Macedonian, Port Praya, West Africa 1844 Jun 14, USS Macedonian, Monrovia, West Afica 1844 Jul 17, USS Macedonian, Monrovia, West Africa 1844 Jul 21, USS Macedonian, Monrovia, West Africa, to [ ] 1844 Sep 23, USS Macedonian, Porto Grande Island off St. Vincent (copy) 1844 Oct 1, USS Macedonian, Porto Grande Island off St. Vincent, to Henry A. Brightman (copy) 1844 Oct 21, USS Macedonian, Porto Grande Island off St. Vincent (copy)
Peters, William H. 1852 Sep 23, Navy Yard, Gosport
Pettit, Robert see Chapman, G.W.
Pike, James Shepherd 1864 Jun 27, The Hague, Netherlands 1864 Aug 25, The Hague, Netherlands (telegram) 1864 Sep 2, The Hague, Netherlands (telegram) 1864 Sep 2, The Hague, Netherlands (telegram) 1864 Sep 2, The Hague, Netherlands (telegram) 1864 Sep 19, The Hague, Netherlands (telegram)
Porter, David Dixon 1869 Mar 13, Navy Department, Washington 1869 Apr 8, Navy Department, Washington (telegram) 1869 May 15, Navy Department, Washington
Preble, George Henry 1869 Apr 22, San Francisco 1869 Apr 23, USS Pensacola, off San Francisco 1869 May 25, USS Pensacola off Mexico 1869 Jun 12, USS Pensacola off San Francisco 1869 Jun 16, USS Pensacola off San Francisco
Prince, George A. 1847 Mar 4, Buffalo, New York, to [John Y. Mason] (copy)
Radford, William 1863 Dec 26, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Jan 2, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Feb 24, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Feb 24, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Mar 7, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Mar 9, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Mar 17, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Mar 17, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Mar 22, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Apr 4, Navy Yard, New York 1864 Apr 16, Navy Yard, New York
Richardson, A. H. 1869 Jun 8, San Francisco 1869 Jun 10, San Francisco 1869 Jun 12, San Francisco 1869 Jul 28, Vallejo, California
Roberts, Joseph Jenkins 1844 ca. Jan, [ ], to [R. T.] Sims (copy) 1844 Jan 13, Gov't House, Monrovia, W. Africa
Russell, John Russell, 1st earl 1863 Jan 15, Foreign Office, London, to Charles Francis Adams 1864 Aug 23, Foreign Office, London, to Charles Francis Adams (copy)
Salter, William D. 1851 Jun 18, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Jul 25, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Jul 29, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Jul 30, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Jul 31, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Aug 4, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Aug 5, Navy Yard, New York 1851 Sep 19, Navy Yard, New York
Sanford, Henry Shelton 1864 Jun 1, Brussels (telegram) 1864 Jul 1, Brussels 1864 Jul 14, Brussels 1864 Oct 15, Brussels (telegram) 1864 Dec 31, Brussels 1865 Jan 29, Brussels 1865 Jan 30, Brussels (telegram) 1865 Feb 2, Brussels (telegram) 1865 Feb 5, Brussels (telegram) 1865 Feb 17, Paris (telegram) 1865 Jul 31, Brussels, to William H. Seward
Sauer, — 1864 Dec 2, Legation of US, Paris (telegram)
Savage, Thomas 1864 Nov 19, Havana, to Gideon Welles 1864 Nov 20, Havana, to Hiram Paulding
Shirley, Paul 1868 Jun 10, USS Pensacola, off San Francisco
Shufeldt, Robert Wilson 1864 Mar, [ ], to William Radford
Simms, John D. 1841 Sep 27, Navy Dept.
Simpson, Edward 1869 Jan 19, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Sims (?), R.T. 1844 Jan 24, Mesurado Roads, W. Africa, to Joseph Jenkins Roberts (copy) 1844 Jan 29, Cape Palmas, to Matthew C. Perry
Sisco, Pierre 1864 Sep 8, Dover, England 1865 Jan 31, Dover, England (copy) (with Labado to Sisco, 1865, Jan 27)
Smith, A. N. 1863 Oct 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Nov 11, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Jan 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 6, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 8, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 9, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 19, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 25, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Mar 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Mar 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 7, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Pierce Archer, Jr. 1864 May 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to William Gaston Steele 1864 May 28, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Sep 28, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1865 Mar 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Smith, A. Thomas 1843 Jun 23, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Matthew C. Perry
Smith, G. 1864 Mar 31, USS Niagara at sea, to Henry Erben
Smith, James 1864 Feb 22, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Smith, Joseph 1865 Sep 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Smith, Melancton 1868 Jul 20, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Commanding Officer, North Pacific Squadron 1868 Jul 21, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Jul 28, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Henry Knot Thatcher 1868 Jul 31, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Aug 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Aug 18, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Sep 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 3, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 12, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 17, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Nov 3, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Nov 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 7, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Feb 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Feb 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Feb 17, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Sotomaior, Antonio Maria da Cunha Pereira de 1864 Feb 17, New York 1864 Feb 27, New York
Stellwagen, H. S. 1843 Oct 24, US Brig Porpoise, Monrovia, W. Africa
Stillwell, Silas Moore 1844 Nov 21, US Marshall's Office, S. District of New York
Stribling, C. K. 1851 Jul 21, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1851 Jul 29, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1851 Aug 26, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1851 Aug 26, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1851 Sep 6, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1851 Sep 6, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1852 Jun 14, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1852 Jun 18, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1852 Jun 21, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1852 Sep 11, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD 1852 Sep 11, U. S. Naval Academy, Annapolis, MD
Stringham, Silas Horton 1864 Sep 28, U. S. Navy Yard, Boston 1865 Sep 22, U. S. Navy Yard, Boston 1865 Sep 25, U. S. Navy Yard, Boston
Tabor, J. W. 1869 Jan 13, Treasury Dept. [Washington], to Gideon Welles
Tattnall, Josiah 1844 Mar 8, USS Saratoga, Cape Mesurado, W. Africa, to Charles Heywood, Charles Boggs, & Horatio Bridge (copy) 1844 Mar 11, USS Saratoga, Mesurado Roads, W. Africa, to Matthew C. Perry 1844 Jun 28, USS Saratoga
Thatcher, Henry Knox 1868 Jul 30, USS Pensacola
Turner, Thomas 1868 Jul 22, USS Pouhatan on her passage to Payta, Panama 1869 Sep 25, USS Pensacola off Mare Island, Calif. 1869 Sep 25, USS Pensacola off Mare Island, Calif. 1869 Sep 25, USS Pensacola off Mare Island, Calif. 1869 Sep 27, USS Pensacola off Mare Island, Calif. 1869 Oct 5, USS Pensacola off Mare Island, Calif.
Valiant, William Thomas 1861 Jun 5, Custom House, Baltimore, to Salmon P. Chase (copy)
Van Dyk, Walter 1869 Aug 5, San Francisco, to [George M. Robeson] (copy)
Vendroux, [ ] 1864 Dec 26, Calais, France, to John Bigelow 1864 Dec 29, Calais, France, to U. S. Minister at Brussels 1864 Dec 29, Calais, France, to Consular Agency of the United States 1865 Jan 5, Calais, France
Walke, Henry 1864 Jul 22, USS Sacramento 1864 Jul 31, USS Sacramento 1864 Aug 31, USS Sacramento (plus a copy) 1864 Sep 13, France (telegram) 1864 Sep 17, USS Sacramento 1864 Sep 23, USS Sacramento 1864 Oct 4, USS Sacramento 1864 Oct 29, USS Sacramento 1864 Nov 1, USS Sacramento 1864 Nov 7, USS Sacramento 1864 Nov 16, USS Sacramento 1865 Jan 26, USS Sacramento 1865 Feb 15, USS Sacramento
Ward, Edward C., Jr. 1844 Jun 3, US Brig Dolphin, at sea
Ward, James Harmon 1861 Jun 12, Washington, to Gideon Welles (copy)
Warner, Robert 1865 Jun 13, Cork
Warrington, Lewis 1844 Mar 15, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Matthew C. Perry (copy)
Watkins, M. Carrington 1844 Jun 26, US Brig Porpoise, at sea
Welles, Gideon 1861 Apr 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Samuel L. Breese 1861 May 17, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to William Budd 1861 May 18, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1861 Jun 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to James H. Ward 1861 Jun 6, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to James H. Ward 1861 Jun 18, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to James H. Ward 1861 Jun 18, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to J. C. Rowan 1863 Feb 17, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to John B. Montgomery (printed circular) 1863 Jun 9, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Jun 22, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Jun 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Oct 7, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Oct 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Oct 24, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Oct 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Oct 30, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Nov 2, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Nov 6, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Dec 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1863 Dec 11, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (telegram) 1863 Dec 24, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (plus a copy) 1863 Dec 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Jan 5, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Feb 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Mar 8, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 20, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Apr 30, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 May 24, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 May 30, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Aug 15, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Aug 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Aug 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Aug 19, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Oct 22, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Nov 28, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Nov 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Dec 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1864 Dec 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1865 Jan 17, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1865 Feb 25, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1865 Sep 26, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1865 Nov 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (telegram) 1868 Mar 24, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 May 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Jul 11, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Jul 15, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Jul 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Henry Knox Thatcher 1868 Aug 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Aug 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (copy) 1868 Sep 8, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Sep 9, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (telegram) 1868 Sep 9, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Sep 11, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Sep 12, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (printed circular) 1868 Oct 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 7, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 13, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Oct 22, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Nov 2, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Nov 10, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 3, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 3, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 7, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 9, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1868 Dec 14, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 6, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 16, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 20, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 27, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Jan 28, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Feb 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C., to Hugh McCulloch (copy) 1869 Feb 1, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Feb 4, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. (telegram) 1869 Feb 6, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C. 1869 Mar 3, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Wilding, H. G. 1864 Aug 8, Liverpool, England 1864 Aug 26, Liverpool, England 1864 Oct 12, Liverpool, England (telegram) 1865 Mar 14, Liverpool, England, to Horatio J. Perry (copy) (with Perry to TTC, 1865 Mar 18)
Winslow, John Ancrum 1864 Jul 21, USS Kearsarge 1864 Jul 28, USS Kearsarge
Wise, Henry Augustus 1865 Dec 29, Navy Dept., Washington, D. C.
Index to General Orders, notes, etc
Craven, Thomas Tingey1843 Oct 31, Internal Rules & Reg. on board the US Brig Porpoise, to all those under the command of TTC 1843 Mar 31, General Order (hereafter G. O.), to All Capts., Commanders, & C. O. of His Majesty's Ships
Henshaw, David 1843 Oct 11, Navy Department, Washington D. C., to Matthew C. Perry (copy) 1844 Jan 20, Navy Reg: Undress Uniform & Chaplains Uniform, to ---
King of Spain 1861 Jul 29, Proclamation, to Ministry of Foreign Affairs
Perry, Matthew C. ---, Extract from letter of Capt. Foote, R. M., to ---
Perry, Matthew C., USS Saratoga 1843 Jun 21, G. O. #1, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Jul 3, G. O. #2, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Jul 10, G. O. #4, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Jul 31, G. O. #5, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Aug 1, G. O. #6, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron
Perry, Matthew C., USS Macedonia 1843 Sep 1, G. O. #7, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Sep 14, G. O. #9, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Nov 18, G. O. #10, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Nov 24, Additional G. O., to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Nov 30, G. O. #11, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1843 Nov 6, G. O. #12, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1844 Mar 2, G. O. #13, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron 1844 Mar 6, G. O. #14, to C. O. of all US vessel attached to the African Squadron 1844 Sep 16, G. O. #19, to C. O. of all US vessels attached to the African Squadron
Rodgers, William P. ---, US Navy Rules & Reg., Chapter #20, to Submitted to Congress
Witnesses, US Brig Uncas 1843 Dec 31, Testimony on the murder of Mr. (Mate) Richardson by Robert G. Standon, to all concerned
[unidentified] 1864 Oct 14, Description of the Sea King wood screw steamer